mashvisor.com 2015-06-01

# Privacy Policy | Mashvisor

**YOUR PRIVACY IS NOT FOR SALE**

We do not and will not sell or rent your personal information to anyone, for any reason, at any time. Mashvisor uses and discloses your personal information only as follows:

  * unless you ask us not to, we may contact you via email in the future to tell you about specials, new service offerings, or changes to this privacy policy;
  * to analyze site usage and improve the Service;
  * to deliver to you any administrative notices, alerts and communications relevant to your use of the Service;
  * to fulfill your requests for certain services and transactions;
  * for market research, project planning, troubleshooting problems, detecting and protecting against error, fraud or other criminal activity;
  * to enforce Mashvisor’s Terms of Use; and
  * as otherwise set forth in this Privacy Policy.

In the event that you access the Service as brought to you by our partners or service providers, through a co-branded URL or by web services, your email address used for registration on the Service may be provided to that partner or service provider to fulfill your request.

HOW WE LIMIT THE COLLECTION AND USE OF PERSONAL INFORMATION

Certain areas and features of [Mashvisor.com](http://mashvisor.com/) are available to you without registration or the need to provide to us any information. However, other features of the Site or the Service may require registration, which involves provision to Mashvisor of an email address, a password and additional details for fulfilling your service requests and to participate on our third party sites, a username (collectively the “Registration or Sign Up Information”). In order to benefit from the full functionality of the Service, you may also be asked to provide additional information to all Mashvisor to share more data for your use.

From time to time we may request other personal information to provide you with other benefits of the Service such as application for a loan or payment instructions for purchasing a property. In all such instances, you will be given the opportunity to provide or to decline to provide that information, and it will be used only for the stated purpose. By providing the information, you are also agreeing to share the information with other Service providers such as Property Provider, lender, insurance company, Title company, Escrow/ Closing Attorney, inspection company, appraisal company and others.

Mashvisor may make anonymous or aggregate personal information and disclose such data only in a non-personally identifiable manner to:

  * Advertisers and other third parties for marketing and promotional purposes, such as the number of users who applied for a loan or how many users clicked on a particular Offer from Mashvisor;
  * Organizations approved by Mashvisor that conduct research into investment purchases; and
  * Users of the Service for purposes of comparison of their personal financial situation relative to the broader market.

Such information does not identify you individually. Access to your Registration Information, other Credentials, and any other personal information you provide is strictly restricted and used in accordance with specific internal procedures and safeguard governing access, in order to operate, develop or improve the Service. These individuals have been selected in accordance with our security policies and practices and are bound by confidentiality obligations. We may also use third party vendors or service providers to help us provide the Service to you, such as sending e-mail messages on our behalf or hosting and operating a particular feature or functionality of the Service or a lender processing your loan application. Our contracts with these third parties outline the appropriate use and handling of your information and prohibit them from using any of your personal information for purposes unrelated to the product or service they’re providing. We require such third parties to maintain the confidentiality of the information we provide to them.

HOW YOU CAN CHANGE YOUR REGISTRATION INFORMATION 

If your Registration Information changes during your subscription to Mashvisor, you may update it any time via the Service.

HOW WE USE ONLINE SESSION INFORMATION TO IMPROVE YOUR EXPERIENCE

When you visit [Mashvisor.com](http://mashvisor.com/), we may collect technical and navigational information, such as computer browser type, Internet protocol address, pages visited, and average time spent on our Site. This information may be used, for example, to alert you to software compatibility issues, or it may be analyzed to improve our Web design and functionality.

“Cookies” are alphanumeric identifiers in the form of text files that are inserted and stored by your Web browser on your computer’s hard drive. Mashvisor may set and access cookies on your computer to track and store preferential information about you. Mashvisor may gather information about you through cookie technology. For example, Mashvisor may assign a cookie to you, to limit the amount of times you see a particular Mashvisor Offer or to help better determine which Mashvisors Offers to serve to you. Please note that most Internet browsers will allow you to stop cookies from being stored on your computer or device and to delete cookies stored on your computer or device. If you choose to eliminate cookies, the full functionality of the Service may be impaired for you.

We encode our cookies so that only we can interpret the information stored in them.

Web beacons or zero or single byte tags are embedded in a Web page or email for the purpose of measuring and analyzing site usage and activity. Mashvisor, or third party service providers acting on our behalf, may use Web beacons to help us analyze Site usage and improve the Service.

We may use third party service providers to help us analyze certain online activities. For example, these service providers may help us measure the performance of our online and email campaigns or analyze visitor activity on [Mashvisor.com](http://mashvisor.com/) and related sites. We may permit these service providers to use cookies and other technologies to perform these services for Mashvisor. We do not share any personal information about our customers with these third party service providers, and these service providers do not collect such information on our behalf. Our third party service providers are required to comply fully with this Privacy Policy.

THIRD PARTIES OFFERING OTHER SERVICES WILL NOT BE GIVEN YOUR PERSONAL INFORMATION WITHOUT YOUR PERMISSION

There are a number of separate products and services offered by third parties advertised by us on our Site and through the Service that may be complementary to your use of [Mashvisor.com](http://mashvisor.com/), such as lenders, investment companies, retirement services providers, and brokerage institutions (collectively, “Mashvisor Offers”). If you choose to use these separate products or services, disclose information to the providers, or grant them permission to collect information about you, then their use of your information is governed by their privacy policies. You should evaluate the practices of external services providers before deciding to use their services. Mashvisor is not responsible for their privacy practices. If you click on a link to a third party site, Mashvisor encourages you to check the privacy policy of that site. Mashvisor may present links in a format that enables us to keep track of whether these links have been followed and whether any action has been taken on a third party Web site. We use this information to improve the quality of the Mashvisor Offers and customized content on the Service.

SOCIAL MEDIA AND BLOG ON Mashvisor.COM

If you use a social media, bulletin board, blog or chat room from our Site, you should be aware that any information you submit there can be read, collected or used by other users and could be used to send you unsolicited messages. We are not responsible for the personal information you choose to submit in these online media. These media may be hosted by Mashvisor or by a third party service providers.

CONTESTS, GIVEAWAYS, SURVEYS AND FEEDBACK

From time to time, Mashvisor may offer you the opportunity to participate in contests, giveaways and other promotions. Any information submitted in connection with such activities will be treated in accordance with this Privacy Policy, except as specifically set forth in the rules for those contests, giveaways or promotions. From time to time, Mashvisor may also ask you to participate in surveys and feedback designed to help Mashvisor improve the Site. Any personal information provided to Mashvisor in connection with any survey will be used only in relation to that survey and as elsewhere set forth in this Policy.

CHILDREN’S PRIVACY

For protecting the privacy of young children, Mashvisor does not knowingly collect or solicit personal information from anyone under the age of 13. If you are under 13, do not share any information about yourself to us, including your name, address, telephone number, or email address. No one under age 13 is allowed to provide any personal information to Mashvisor. In the event that we learn that we have collected personal information from a child under age 13 without verification of parental consent, we will delete that information as quickly as possible. As a parent you are responsible for any transactions or services requested from Mashvisor.

DISCLOSURE OF YOUR INFORMATION TO PROTECT OUR RIGHTS OR IF REQUIRED BY LAW

Notwithstanding the foregoing, Mashvisor reserves the right (and you authorize Mashvisor) to share or disclose your personal information when Mashvisor determines, in its sole discretion, that the disclosure of such information is necessary or appropriate:

  * To enforce our rights against you or in connection with a breach by you of this Privacy Policy or the[Mashvisor.com](http://mashvisor.com/) Terms of Use;
  * To prevent prohibited or illegal transaction or activities; or
  * When required by any applicable law, rule regulation, subpoena or other legal process.

YOUR DATA MAY BE TRANSFERRED UPON CHANGE OF CONTROL BUT ONLY IN ACCORDANCE WITH THIS POLICY 

Personal information may be transferred to a third party as a result of a sale, acquisition, merger, reorganization or other change of control. If we sell, merge or transfer any part of our business, part of the sale may include your personal information. If so, you will be asked if you’d like to stop receiving promotional information following any change of control.

YOU CAN TRANSPORT OR DELETE YOUR DATA 

Your data is yours. You can request us to remove it anytime you want. When you request us to delete your account for the Service, your data will be permanently expunged from our primary production servers and further access to your account will not be possible. We will also promptly disconnect any connection we had established to your Account Information and delete all related credentials. However, portions of your data, consisting of aggregate data derived from your Account Information, may remain on our production servers indefinitely. Your data may also remain on a backup server or media. Mashvisor keeps these backups to ensure our continued ability to provide the Service to you in the event of malfunction or damage to our primary production servers. We also reserve the right to use any aggregated or anonymous data derived from or incorporating your personal information.

ELECTRONIC COMMUNICATIONS FROM US 

We provide our registered customers with periodic newsletter, summaries of their property portfolios and email alerts. We also allow users to subscribe to email newsletters and from time to time may transmit emails promoting Mashvisor or third-party goods or services. [Mashvisor.com](http://mashvisor.com/) subscribers have the ability to opt-out of receiving our promotional emails and to terminate their subscriptions by following the instructions in the emails. Opting out in this manner will not end transmission of service-related emails, such as email alerts.

YOUR DATA IS SECURE 

We use a combination of firewall barriers, encryption techniques and authentication procedures, among others, to maintain the security of your online session and to protect [Mashvisor.com](http://mashvisor.com/) accounts and systems from unauthorized access.

When you register for the Service, Mashvisor requires a password from you for your privacy and security.

Our servers are in a secure facility. Access requires multiple levels of authentication.

Our databases are protected from general employee access both physically and logically. We encrypt your Service password so that your password cannot be recovered, even by us. All backup data are also encrypted.

We enforce physical access controls to our buildings.

However, it is important to understand that these precautions apply only to our Site and systems. We exercise no control over how your information is stored, maintained or displayed by third parties or on third-party sites.

YOU ARE RESPONSIBLE FOR MAINTAINING THE CONFIDENTIALITY OF YOUR LOGIN ID, PASSWORD OR ANY LINKS SENT TO YOU RELATED TO YOUR INFORMATION

We maintain strict rules to help prevent others from guessing your password. We also recommend that you change your password periodically. Your password must be 6-8 characters in length. You are responsible for maintaining the security of your Login ID and Password. You may not provide these credentials to any third party. If you believe that they have been stolen or been made known to others, you must contact us immediately at [privacy@mashvisor.com](mailto:privacy@mashvisor.com). In any event you should change your password immediately via the Service. We are not responsible if someone else accesses your account through Registration Information they have obtained from you or through a violation by you of this Privacy Policy or the [Mashvisor.com](http://mashvisor.com/) Terms of Use.

If you are forwarding any links related to data or otherwise provided by Mashvisor, you are doing so at your own risk. Mashvisor cannot be held liable for any consequences of such sharing.

If you have a security related concern, please contact us at [Privacy@Mashvisor.com](mailto:Privacy@Mashvisor.com). We will work closely with you to ensure a rapid and personal response to your concerns.

WE POST UPDATES ON OUR WEBSITE WHENEVER THERE IS A CHANGE TO OUR PRIVACY AND SECURITY POLICY

We update this Privacy & Security Policy periodically. The date last revised appears at the top of the Policy. Changes take effect immediately upon posting.

CONTACT US IF YOU HAVE ANY QUESTIONS OR CONCERNS

If you have questions, comments, concerns or feedback regarding this Privacy and Security Policy or any other privacy or security concern, send an e-mail to: [Privacy@Mashvisor.com](mailto:Privacy@Mashvisor.com).
